mediajobsearchcanada.com 2015-12-10

# Privacy Policy - Media Job Search Canada

## Privacy Policy

All personal information on Resumes posted on **Media Job Search Canada Inc.'s** corporate websites; [www.mediajobsearchcanada.com](http://www.mediajobsearchcanada.com/) / [www.mediajobsearchcanada.net](http://www.mediajobsearchcanada.net/) / [www.mjsc.ca](http://www.mjsc.ca/) is protected by the **Government of Canada's Internet Privacy Act.**   

**MJSC** does not share or distribute any of this personal information to outside companies.

For more information on **MJSC's Privacy Statement** in full read the complete statement below.

For more information on the "Internet Privacy Act" visit:  [www.privcom.gc.ca](http://www.privcom.gc.ca/)

###    
Updated August  1, 2015.

Your privacy is very important to us. Rest assured that all information collected through our **( 1 )** visitor tracking program, the personal information provided on **( 2 )** posted resumes and the username and password information through our **( 3 )**  client login information remains with Media Job Search Canada Inc. and is never shared with outside sources.

**(1)** When you visit our website our visitor tracking program monitors how many times you have visited, how long you stayed and what pages you are visiting. This is done by the signature or IP address assigned to you by your internet connection provider, via your computer. At no time does this program have access to your name, address and phone number or any other personal information that may be used against you by a malicious third party.

**(2)** You are in control of all the information you provide when you post a resume on our website. Although our on-line resume form requires certain information, we suggest that if you are worried about personal security that you only supply the necessary information you feel is required to attract the attention of employers, especially when providing a reliable contact source.

**(3)** When a resume is posted on our website, (just like you did when you first posted your resume), only those people who have signed up with a username (e-mail address) and password can view the resumes. We monitor the activity of this service and if we feel that any account is being abused we contact the user to confirm that they are the person using the access codes, especially if their usage is unusually high. Access accounts that are being used maliciously will be cancelled.

If you have any questions on this statement, please contact us for more information [mjsc@mediajobsearchcanada.com](mailto:mjsc@mediajobsearchcanada.com)

**Corey Fuchs - Owner, President & C.E.O.**  
**Media Job Search Canada Inc.**
